<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="hotel_category">Hotels</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Food</string>
    <string name="shop_category">Shops</string>
    <string name="info_category">Info</string>

    <string name="first_res_name">Dinner by Heston Blumenthal</string>
    <string name="first_res_about">The restaurant is the birthplace of “new Nordic” cuisine, which relies
        solely on ingredients available in region.</string>

    <string name="second_res_name">Restaurant Gordon Ramsay</string>
    <string name="second_res_about">Behind a stately exterior, the world’s most emotive chef, Massimo Bottura,
        cooks flights of fantasy and memory.</string>

    <string name="third_res_name">The French Laundry</string>
    <string name="third_res_about">Heston Blumenthal took his fascination with English culinary history and
        turned it into something unexpectedly interesting for the rest of us.</string>

    <string name="four_res_name">Victors Fine Dining</string>
    <string name="four_res_about">Grant Achatz did a brief stint at Ferran Adriàs elBulli, and ever since
        has been out avant-garding what was once the most avant-garde restaurant in the world. </string>

    <string name="five_res_name">The Test Kitchen</string>
    <string name="five_res_about"> The Ledbury is probably the most classical, which is to say that its chef,
        Australian-born Brett Graham, is more interested in pleasure than wizardry. </string>


    <string name="first_hotel_name">Alvear Palace</string>
    <string name="first_hotel_about">The hotel was constructed by Las Vegas Sands and is managed by Starwood Hotels
        . It is part of Macaus newest fully integrated resort complex, Sands Cotai Central.</string>

    <string name="second_hotel_name">Armenia Marriott Hotel</string>
    <string name="second_hotel_about">The resort was originally designed by architect Jon Jerde in collaboration with Steve
        Wynn along with Roger Thomas who designed the interior of Treasure Island Hotel and Casino.</string>

    <string name="third_hotel_name">The Hotel Windsor</string>
    <string name="third_hotel_about">The JW Marriott Marquis Dubai Hotel is the worlds tallest hotel, a 72-storey, 355 m
        (1,165 ft) twin-tower skyscraper complex in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. </string>

    <string name="four_hotel_name">Grand Hotel London</string>
    <string name="four_hotel_about"> During the colonial period, The Strand was one of the most luxurious hotels in the
        British Empire with a clientele of exclusively whites.</string>

    <string name="five_hotel_name">Great Western Royal</string>
    <string name="five_hotel_about">The Savoy Hotel was the first in the Savoy group of hotels and restaurants owned
        by Cartes family for over a century.</string>


    <string name="first_shop_name"> Kith NYC</string>
    <string name="first_shop_about">Ronnie Fieg and crew have not only established a brand that cancreate
        pieces that sell outin a matter of minutes,but he is also created a shop that gives other
        NYC shops who have been around for years a run for their money. </string>

    <string name="second_shop_name">Fruition LV</string>
    <string name="second_shop_about">The best heritage brands? Got em. Japanese favorites? Filled to the
        brim. Exclusive collaborations with flat out winning brands?</string>

    <string name="third_shop_name">Carson Street Clothiers</string>
    <string name="third_shop_about">One of the newest shops around will have you feeling laid back
        and anxious to get your hands on their menswear mix at the same time</string>

    <string name="four_shop_name">Marks &amp; Spencer</string>
    <string name="four_shop_about">Carrying the staple streetwear brands before you even knew what streetwear was. </string>

    <string name="five_shop_name">Maadi City Center</string>
    <string name="five_shop_about">The bespoke tailor and shirt maker offers a luxurious experience throughout
        it\'s four-story shop. </string>


    <!-- Phone Number Strings -->
    <string name="first_phone_number">+92 548 784</string>
    <string name="second_phone_number">+78 174 295</string>
    <string name="third_phone_number">+34 162 133</string>
    <string name="four_phone_number">+01 550 641</string>
    <string name="five_phone_number">+68 149 443</string>

    <!-- Locations Strings -->
    <string name="first_location">+92 548 784</string>
    <string name="second_location">+78 174 295</string>
    <string name="third_location">+34 162 133</string>
    <string name="four_location">+01 550 641</string>
    <string name="five_location">+68 149 443</string>

    <!-- Reviews Strings -->
    <string name="first_review">914 LIKES</string>
    <string name="second_review">804 LIKES</string>
    <string name="third_review">757 LIKES</string>
    <string name="four_review">736 LIKES</string>
    <string name="five_review">422 LIKES</string>

    <string name="share_string">SHARE</string>
    
    <!-- Info Strings -->

    <string name="inf_about_header">About The City</string>
    <string name="info_about">
        This is just a fictional Place :) .
        A fictional country is a country that is made up for fictional stories, and does not exist in
        real life, or one that people believe in without proof(Wiki).
       Fictional countries appear commonly in stories of early science fiction (or scientific romance).
        Such countries supposedly form part of the normal Earth landscapealthough not located in a normal
        atlas. Later similar tales often took place on fictional planets(Wiki).

    </string>

    <string name="info_location_header">Location Info</string>
    <string name="info_location">
        Our beautiful city also has a fictional location :) .
        Fictional locations are places that exist only in fiction and not in reality, such as the Negaverse or
        Planet X. Writers may create and describe such places to serve as backdrop for their fictional works. Fictional
        locations are also created for use as settings in role-playing games such as Dungeons and Dragons(Wiki).
    </string>

    <string name="info_general_header">General Info</string>
    <string name="info_general">
        This is a random generated text:
        Smallest directly families surprise honoured am an. Speaking replying mistress him numerous she returned feelings may day.
        Evening way luckily son exposed get general greatly. Zealously prevailed be arranging do. Set arranging too dejection
        september happiness. Understood instrument or do connection no appearance do invitation. Dried quick round it or order.
        Add past see west felt did any. Say out noise you taste merry plate you share. My resolve arrived is we chamber be removal.

    </string>

</resources>
